Kundwa Bruno Materne

Fullstack Software Engineer

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 3 years of related experience.

Relevant experience

2021-10 -Current

Frontend Developer

Awesomity Lab, Kigali, Kigali

- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- Developed designs to meet specific requirements such as quick-loading sites with particular layouts.
- Reviewed and tested customer-facing prototypes before deployment, applying best practice diagnostic techniques to verify usability.

2021-02 -2021-11

Fullstack Developer

Techenfold, Kigali, Rwanda

- Collaborated on the core functionality of the whole application (both ends) Performing pull requests, code reviews, and pair programming to provide meaningful feedback to team members Contributing to Developing a Multi-functioning platform for E-learning activities
- Managed development milestones from initial steps through final delivery.
- Consulted with engineering team members to determine system loads and develop improvement plans.

2020-01 -2021-02

Fullstack Developer

Andela, Kigali, Rwanda

- I was a Team Lead For Several Sprints, Which provided me with Leadership skills such as Project management skills.
- Managed development milestones from initial steps through final delivery.
- Consulted with engineering team members to determine system loads and develop improvement plans.

Education

2021-08 -Current

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

Adventist University of Central Africa - Rwanda

Member of Information Technology club.

2017-01 -2019-11

High School Diploma

Nu-vision High School - Rwanda

- Relevant Coursework Completed: Maths, Economics & Computer science.
- Elected to Asst president for ICDL club in 2019.
- Completed professional development in Visual basic.

Contact

Address

Kigali, Rwanda

Phone

250-789-070593

E-mail

kundwabruno@gmail.com

Twitte

https://twitter.com/bruno_kbm

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kundwabruno/

www

https://www.itskbm.com/

Skills

Programming languages

- Javascript (ES6)
- Typescript
- HTML
- CSS/SASS

Libraries and Frameworks

- React Js
- Next Js
- Tailwind
- JQuery
- Node Js
- Express

Tools and platforms

- Git/Github
- Firebase
- Heroku
- Netlify

Languages

- English
- French
- KinyaRwanda